RG 005:036, Office of the Governor: Ella Grasso (1975-1980)
Connecticut State Library
- Part III Subject Files, 1974-1981
  - [Criminal Justice - Dept. of Adult Probation] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 542)
  - [Criminal Justice - Pardon] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 542)
  - [Criminal Justice - Parole] (B), 1975-1980 (Box 542)
  - [Day Care] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 543)
  - Deeds (B), 1979 (Box 543)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1979 (Box 543)
  - Development Authority (Conn.) CDA (Box 543)
    - Agenda/Minutes (Box 543)
      - Special meeting, 1978 November 2 (Box 544)
      - Special meeting, 1978 November 20 (Box 544)
      - 1979 January-July (Box 545)
      - Misc., [undated] (Box 546)
      - Misc., [undated] (Box 546)
  - [Development Authority] (Conn.) - [CEA - Audit], 1978 (Box 546)
  - [Drinking Age Letters] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 546)
  - [Eastern States Exposition], 1980 (Box 546)
  - Economic Development & Authority - EDA (B), 1979 (Box 546)
  - Economic Development - Memos to and from Duffy, 1975-1977 (Box 546)
  - Economic Development/Miles lab luncheon (O), 1979 September 13 (Box 546)
  - [Economic Development - Misc.], 1980 (Box 546)
  - [Education] (Box 547)
    - [Budgets], 1980 (Box 547)
    - [Camp School, New Britain] (B) (Box 547)
    - [Central Conn. State College] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 547)
    - [Commission of the States], 1980 (Box 547)
    - [Commission on Higher Education - Letters] (Box 547)
      - A-H, 1979-1980 (Box 547)
      - I-Z (B), 1979-1980 (Box 547)
    - [Community Colleges, Board of Trustees], 1978-1979 (Box 547)
    - [Community Colleges, Misc.] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 547)
    - Conn. Education Council, 1979 (Box 547)
    - [Conn. State Board of Education], 1979-1981 (Box 547)
    - [Education Commission of the States], 1979 (Box 548)
    - [Elementary/Secondary Education Plan], 1979 (Box 548)
    - [Letters] (Box 548)
      - A-H (B), 1979-1980 (Box 548)
      - I-O (B), 1978-1980 (Box 548)
    - Marivon School, 1979 (Box 548)
    - [Memos to and from Shedd], 1978-1980 (Box 548)
    - [Miscellaneous] (B), 1978-1981 (Box 549)
    - Mystic Oral School, 1979 (Box 549)
    - [Presidential Classroom for Young Americans], 1980 (Box 549)
    - [Proposed Aircraft School, Stratford] (B), 1980 (Box 549)
    - Regional Community College Budget, 1979 (Box 549)
    - [School Health Task Force], 1979 (Box 549)
    - [Southern Conn. State College] (B), 1979 (Box 549)
    - Special Education Contract, Norwalk (I), 1980 (Box 549)
    - [State Aid to Towns] (I), 1981 (Box 549)
    - [State Aid to Towns - New Canaan] (I), 1981 (Box 549)
    - [State Colleges, Board of Trustees] (B), 1979 (Box 550)
    - Teacher’s Retirement] (B), 1979 (Box 550)
    - [UCONN] (Box 550)
      - Board of Trustees Meeting (O), 1980 November 14 (Box 550)
      - [Health Center A-Z] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 550)
      - [Health Center Misc.], 1979-1980 (Box 550)
      - [Letters A-Z] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 550)
      - [Library] (B), 1980 (Box 550)
      - [Miscellaneous] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 550)
      - [University of Hartford], 1980 (Box 550)
    - [Vet School] (B), 1979 (Box 550)
    - [Vocational Rehabilitation], 1979 (Box 550)
    - [Vocational/Technical Schools] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 550)
    - [Western Conn. State College] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 551)
    - [Yale] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 551)
    - Yale Students, Gun Control (O), 1978 (Box 551)
  - [Elections] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 551)
  - [Employment] (B), 1979 (Box 551)
  - [Employment] (B) (Box 551)
    - Board of Registration for Professional Engineers & Land Surveyors, 1979 (Box 551)
  - Energy - CONEG (B), 1979 October (Box 551)
  - [Environment - DEP] (Box 551)
    - A-B (B), 1979 (Box 551)
    - C-D (B), 1978-1980 (Box 551)
    - E-H (B), 1979-1980 (Box 552)
    - I-L (B), 1978-1979 (Box 552)
    - M-P (B), 1979-1980 (Box 552)
    - R-S (B), 1979-1980 (Box 552)
    - T-Z (B), 1979-1980 (Box 552)
  - [Environment - DEP] (Box 553)
    - Bauca Island (B), 1979 (Box 553)
    - Bristol Landfill, 1979 (Box 553)
    - [Clean Air/Air Quality] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 553)
    - [Coastal Management] (Box 553)
    - [Colchester Landfill] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 553)
    - Colchester Landfill (B), 1980 January (Box 553)
    - Compo Cove (B), 1980 (Box 553)
    - [Conn. Resource Recovery Authority CRRA], 1979-1980 (Box 553)
    - [Conn. River Diversion], 1979 (Box 553)
    - [Conservation/Milford Point] (O), 1979 (Box 553)
    - [Council on Environmental Quality CEO] (B), 1979 (Box 553)
    - [Dams] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 553)
    - [East Windsor Landfill] (B), 1979 (Box 553)
    - [Flooding/Flood Control] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 553)
    - [Hazardous Waste] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 553)
    - [Indian Affairs] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 553)
    - [Long Island Sound/Bridge] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 553)
    - [Memos to and from PAC], 1978-1979 (Box 554)
    - [Miscellaneous] (B), 1978-1980 (Box 554)
    - [Noise Pollution] (B), 1978-1980 (Box 554)
    - North Haven Mall (B), 1979 (Box 554)
    - Orton Farm In Sherman (B), 1979 (Box 554)
    - [Outer Continental Shelf] (B), 1978-1980 (Box 554)
    - [Rivers] (B), 1979 (Box 554)
    - [Safe Boating] (Box 554)
    - [Solid Waste], 1979 (Box 554)
    - Southington Well Contamination, 1979 (Box 554)
    - State Comprehensive Outdoor Recreation Plan, 1979 (Box 554)
    - [State Parks] (B), 1979 (Box 554)
    - [UpJohn Chemical Co.], 1979 (Box 554)
    - [Water Pollution/Quality] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 554)
    - Youth Conservation Corp, 1979 (Box 554)
  - [Equal Rights Amendments] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 554)
  - [Executive Orders], 1974-1979 (Box 554)
  - [Family Relations] (B), 1979 (Box 555)
  - [Families] (Box 555)
    - White House Conference on (WHCF), 1979 (Box 555)
    - WHCF, 1979-1980 (Box 555)
    - WHCF - Proposed Budget & Names of WHCF Participants (Box 555)
    - WHCF Task Force Report, 1980 (Box 555)
  - [Federal Budget] (O), 1979 (Box 555)
  - [Federal Communications Commission], 1979-1980 (Box 555)
  - [Federal Matter - Letters] (Box 555)
    - A-K (B), 1979-1980 (Box 555)
    - L-Z (B), 1979 (Box 555)
  - [Federal Trade Commission], 1979-1980 (Box 555)
  - [Finance Advisory Committee], 1978-1979 (Box 556)
  - Finance Advisory Committee/Minutes of Meeting, 1979 April 4 (Box 556)
  - [Firearms] (B), 1979 (Box 556)
  - [Fire Prevention Committee] (B), 1979 (Box 556)
  - [Flags - Conn.] (B), 1979 (Box 556)
  - [Freedom of Information] (B), 1979 (Box 556)
  - [Get Well Letters] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 556)
  - [Governor - Misc.], 1979 (Box 556)
  - [Governor O’Neill], 1981 (Box 556)
  - Governor, Office of, 1978-1979 (Box 556)
  - [Grants], 1980 (Box 556)
  - Grants, 1980 (Box 556)
  - [Health] (Box 557)
    - CAT Scanner (B), 1980 (Box 557)
    - [Commission on Hospital & Health Care] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 557)
    - [Deaf & Hearing Impaired] (B), 1979 (Box 557)
    - Dental Commission, 1979 (Box 557)
    - [Emergency Services] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 557)
    - [Fluoridation] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 557)
    - [Handicapped] (B), 1979 (Box 557)
    - Laurel Heights (B), 1980 (Box 557)
    - [Mansfield Training School] (B), 1979 (Box 557)
    - [Memos to and from Kerrigan], 1978-1979 (Box 557)
    - [Memos to and from Lloyd], 1978-1979 (Box 557)
    - [Memos to and from Thorne], 1979 (Box 557)
    - [Mental Health] (Box 558)
      - Community Service Grants (B), 1979 (Box 558)
      - [Conn. Valley Hospital] (B), 1979 (Box 558)
      - [Fairfield Hills Hospital] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 558)
      - [Institute of Living] (Box 558)
      - [Letters] (Box 558)
        - A-G (B), 1979 (Box 558)
        - H-M (B), 1979 (Box 558)
        - N-Z (Box 558)
    - [Memos to and from Plant], 1978-1979 (Box 558)
    - [Miscellaneous] (B), 1979 (Box 559)
    - [Norwich State Hospital], 1979 (Box 559)
    - [Transcendental Meditation], 1977-1978 (Box 559)
    - Waterbury YMCA (B), 1980 (Box 559)
    - Mental Retardation/Central Conn. Regional Center, 1979 (Box 559)
    - [Mental Retardation - Dept. Audit], 1979 (Box 559)
    - [Mental Retardation - Letters] (B), 1978-1980 (Box 559)
    - [Mental Retardation - Misc.], 1979-1980 (Box 559)
    - [Merck Foundation] (B), 1979 (Box 559)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1979-1980 (Box 559)
    - [Northwest Conn. Health System Agency], 1979 (Box 559)
    - [Nurses/Nursing] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 559)
    - [Nursing Homes] (B), 1979 (Box 560)
    - [Seaside Regional Center] (B), 1979 (Box 560)
    - [Southbury Training School] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 560)
    - [Statewide Health Coordinating Council] (B), 1979-1981 (Box 560)
    - [Travel Expenses], 1978-1979 (Box 560)
  - [Health, Education, & Welfare - HEW] (Box 560)
    - A-B (B), 1979 (Box 560)
    - F-P (B), 1979-1980 (Box 560)
    - R-T (B), 1979 (Box 560)
  - [HEW - Memos to and from Califano], 1978-1979 (Box 561)
  - [HEW - Miscellaneous], 1979 (Box 561)
  - [HEW - Refugees], 1978-1980 (Box 561)
  - [Health Services] (Box 561)
    - A-B (B), 1979-1980 (Box 561)
    - C-D (B), 1978-1980 (Box 561)
    - E-H (B), 1979-1980 (Box 561)
  - [Health Services] (Box 562)
    - I-L (B), 1979-1980 (Box 562)
    - M-Q (B), 1978-1980 (Box 562)
    - P-S (B), 1979-1980 (Box 562)
    - T-Z (B), 1979-1980 (Box 562)
  - [Heating, Piping & Cooling Work Examining Board] (B), 1978 (Box 562)
  - [Historical - Letters A-Z] (B), 1979 (Box 562)
  - [Historical - Miscellaneous] (B), 1979 (Box 562)
  - [Historical - Old State House] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 562)
  - [Holidays] (B), 1979 (Box 563)
  - [Holocaust] (B), 1979 (Box 563)
  - [Hospices] (B), 1979 (Box 563)
  - [Hostages] (O), 1980 (Box 563)
  - [Housing] (Box 563)
    - Condominium Conversions (B), 1979-1980 (Box 563)
    - [Federal Home Loan Bank], 1979 (Box 563)
    - [Finance Authority - CHFA] (B), 1979 (Box 563)
    - [Letters] (Box 563)
      - A-D (B), 1979 (Box 563)
      - E-L (B), 1978-1979 (Box 563)
      - M-R (B), 1978-1980 (Box 563)
      - S-Z (B), 1979 - 1980 (Box 564)
    - [Memos to and from Sharpe], 1979-1980 (Box 564)
    - [Miscellaneous Correspondence], 1979-1980 (Box 564)
  - [Housing & Urban Development - HUD] (B), 1975-1980 (Box 564)
  - [HUD-701], 1975-1979 (Box 564)
  - [Human Resources - Letters] (Box 564)
    - A-G (B), 1979-1980 (Box 564)
    - H-Z (B), 1979-1980 (Box 564)
    - S-Z (B), 1979-1980 (Box 564)
  - [Human Resources - Memos to and from Manning], 1979-1980 (Box 565)
  - [Human Resources - Miscellaneous], 1980-1981 (Box 565)
  - [Human Resources - Weatherization Program], 1979 (Box 565)
  - [Human Rights & Opportunities (HR & O) - Letters] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 565)
  - [Human Rights & Opportunities - Memos to and from Green], 1978-1979 (Box 565)
  - [Human Rights & Opportunities - Misc.], 1981 (Box 565)
  - Human Services - Annual Agenda for Title XX Mailing List (Box 566)
  - Human Services - (Commission on the Reorganization), 1978-1979 (Box 566)
  - [Human Services - Connecticut Association of], 1980 (Box 566)
  - [Human Services - Misc.], 1979-1980 (Box 566)
  - [Humane Society] (B), 1979 (Box 566)
  - [Humanities Council] (B), 1979 (Box 566)
  - [Income Maintenance] (Box 566)
    - [AFDC] (B), 1979 (Box 566)
    - [Food Stamps] (B), 1979 (Box 566)
    - [Letters] (Box 566)
      - A-C (B), 1978-1979 (Box 566)
      - D-H (B), 1979-1980 (Box 566)
      - I-M, 1978-1979 (Box 567)
      - S-T (B), 1979 (Box 567)
    - [Memos to and from Maher] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 567)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1979 (Box 567)
    - [Press Releases], 1979-1980 (Box 567)
    - [Title XX], 1977-1979 (Box 567)
  - Indochinese Refugees (B), 1979 (Box 567)
  - [Inflation] (B), 1979 (Box 567)
  - [Info Line], 1979-1980 (Box 567)
  - [Information Bureau], 1979 (Box 567)
  - Information Bureau-Commendation Letter (B), 1978 January (Box 567)
  - [Insurance - Letters] (Box 567)
    - A-L, 1979-1980 (Box 567)
    - M-Z (B), 1979-1980 (Box 568)
  - [Intergovernmental Programs] (O), 1978-1979 (Box 568)
  - [Intergovernmental Relations] (O), 1979-1980 (Box 568)
  - [Interior Dept. - U.S.] (O), 1978-1979 (Box 568)
  - [Internal Revenue Service] (B), 1979 (Box 568)
  - International Year of the Child, 1979-1980 (Box 568)
  - [Interstate Commerce Commission], 1980; 2 folders (Box 568)
  - Invitation/Regional Meeting or Export Activities (O), 1979 June 29 (Box 568)
  - [Judicial] (Box 569)
    - [Letters] (Box 569)
      - A-M (O), 1979 (Box 569)
      - N-Z (B), 1979-1980 (Box 569)
    - Litchfield Ct. House (B), 1979-1980 (Box 569)
    - Medical Emergencies (B), 1979 (Box 569)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1979-1981 (Box 569)
    - [Small claims Court] (B), 1979 (Box 569)
  - [Justice - Conn. State Commission On] (B), 1978-1980 (Box 569)
  - [Labor] (Box 569)
    - [CETA Letters] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 569)
    - [CETA Misc.], 1981 (Box 569)
    - [Conn. State Dept. of], 1980 (Box 569)
    - [Letters] (Box 570)
      - A-C (B), 1979-1980 (Box 570)
      - D-I (B), 1979 (Box 570)
      - J-M (B), 1978-1979 (Box 570)
      - N-R (B), 1979 (Box 570)
      - S-Z (B), 1978-1980 (Box 570)
    - [Memos to and from Peraro], 1978-1980 (Box 570)
    - [Memos to and from Santiguido], 1977 (Box 570)
    - [Misc.], 1979-1981 (Box 570)
    - Olin Plant (B), 1979 (Box 570)
    - [Unemployment A-Z] (B), 1979 (Box 570)
    - United Air Lines Strike (B), 1979 (Box 570)
    - [U.S. Dept. of] (Box 570)
    - [Workman’s Compensation/Arbitration] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 570)
  - [Law Enforcement and Assistance Administration], 1978-1979 (Box 571)
  - [Legal] (Box 571)
    - Barbara Gibbons Case (B), 1978 (Box 571)
    - Capital Punishment (B), 1979 (Box 571)
    - [Legal Matter] (Box 571)
      - A-D (B), 1979 (Box 571)
      - E-Z (B) (Box 571)
    - Sunday Closing (Box 571)
      - A-M (B), 1978-1980 (Box 571)
      - N-V (B), 1979-1980 (Box 571)
      - W-Z (B), 1979-1980 (Box 571)
  - [League of Women Voters] (B), 1978 (Box 571)
  - [Library - Letters A-Z] (B), 1978-1980 (Box 571)
  - [Liquor Control Commission - Letters A-Z] (B), 1975-1979 (Box 571)
  - [Local Matters - Letters A-Z] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 572)
  - [Management - Miscellaneous], 1978 (Box 572)
  - [Metric Conversion], 1978 (Box 572)
  - [Military] (Box 572)
    - Army Corps of Engineers/Stamford & New Haven Dredging Project (B), 1979 (Box 572)
    - [Corps of Engineers - N.E. Division], 1979-1980 (Box 572)
    - Helicopter Transportation, 1979 (Box 572)
    - [Letters A-Z] (B), 1978-1980 (Box 572)
    - [Miscellaneous] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 572)
    - [Nautilus] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 572)
  - [Miscellaneous] (Box 572)
  - [Miscellaneous Letters] (Box 572)
    - A-C (B), 1979-1981 (Box 572)
    - D-G (B), 1979-1980 (Box 573)
    - H-K (B), 1979-1980 (Box 573)
    - L-O (B), 1979-1980 (Box 573)
    - P-S (B), 1979-1980 (Box 573)
    - T-Z (B), 1979-1980 (Box 573)
  - [Motor Vehicles - Letters] (Box 573)
    - A-D (B), 1979-1980 (Box 573)
    - E-I (B), 1979-1980 (Box 574)
    - J-O (B), 1979-1980 (Box 574)
    - P-S (B), 1979-1980 (Box 574)
    - T-Z (B), 1979-1980 (Box 574)
  - [Motor Vehicles - Memos to and from Auger & Muzio], 1977-1979 (Box 574)
  - [National Governor’s Association - Misc. Letters] (B), 1978-1980 (Box 574)
  - [National Governor’s Association - Misc. Material], 1978-1980 (Box 575)
  - [National Governor’s Conference] (Box 575)
  - National Youth Science Camp (B), 1978-1979 (Box 575)
  - [Nautilus Committee], 1981 (Box 575)
  - [New Citizens], 1979 (Box 575)
  - New England Congressional Caucus, 1978 (Box 575)
  - [New England Governor’s Association] (Box 575)
    - [Energy Conference] (O), 1978 (Box 575)
    - [Urban Affairs] (O), 1979 (Box 575)
  - [New England Regional Commission] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 575)
  - [New England Resource Agency - Inf. Exchange], 1978-1979 (Box 575)
  - [Northeast - Midwest Congressional Coalition], 1978-1979 (Box 575)
  - [Nuclear Power] (Box 575)
    - [Conn. Yankee], 1978-1979 (Box 575)
    - [Millstone] (Box 575)
  - [Nuclear Power - Nuclear Waste/Radiation] (B), 1979 (Box 576)
  - Office Hours - Governor’s (Box 576)
  - [Office Hours - Letters] (Box 576)
    - A-B (B), 1978-1979 (Box 576)
    - C-E (B), 1978-1979 (Box 577)
    - F-H (B), 1978-1979 (Box 577)
    - I-L (B), 1978-1979 (Box 577)
    - M (B), 1978-1979 (Box 577)
    - N-Q (B), 1978-1979 (Box 577)
    - R-S (B), 1978-1979 (Box 578)
    - T-Z (Box 578)
  - [Office Hours - Towns] (Box 578)
    - [Ansonia] (B), 1978 (Box 578)
    - [Avon] (O), 1979 (Box 578)
    - [Bethel] (O), 1979 (Box 578)
    - [Bristol] (O), 1979 (Box 578)
    - [Colchester] (O), 1978 (Box 578)
    - [East Haven, Ellington] (O), 1978-1979 (Box 578)
    - [Greenwich] (O), 1978 (Box 578)
    - [Groton] (O), 1978 (Box 578)
    - [Guilford] (O), 1979 (Box 578)
    - [Greenwich] (O), 1978 (Box 578)
    - [Groton] (O), 1978 (Box 578)
    - [Guilford] (O), 1979 (Box 578)
    - [Killingly] (O), 1979 (Box 579)
    - Meriden (O), 1978 (Box 579)
    - Middletown (O), 1978 (Box 579)
    - Norwalk (O), 1978 (Box 579)
    - Norwich (O), 1979 December 19 (Box 579)
    - [Old Saybrook] (O), 1979 (Box 579)
    - West Haven (O), 1979 (Box 579)
    - Westport (O), 1979 (Box 579)
    - Willimantic (O), 1978 (Box 579)
    - [Woodbury] (O), 1978 (Box 579)
  - [Office of Management & Budget - Federal], 1980 (Box 579)
  - [Office of Policy & Management - OPM] (Box 579)
    - CETA legislation (O), 1978 (Box 579)
  - [Office of Policy & Management - DPM] (Box 579)
    - [Energy]: (Box 579)
      - Alliance Steering Committee, 1978 (Box 579)
      - [Conservation], 1979-1980 (Box 579)
      - Emergency, 1979 (Box 579)
      - [Emergency Assistance], 1978-1979 (Box 579)
      - Emergency Declaration, 1979 (Box 579)
      - Federal Emergency Conservation Plans (to Congressional (O) (Box 579)
      - [Four Day Work Week] (B), 1979 (Box 580)
      - Fuel Assistance (B), 1979 (Box 580)
      - [Gas Prices], 1979-1980 (Box 580)
      - Gas Pricing Investigation Task Force, 1979 (Box 580)
      - [Gas Rationing], 1979-1980 (Box 580)
      - [Independence], 1981 (Box 580)
      - [Letters] (Box 580)
        - A (B), 1979 (Box 580)
        - Ba (B), 1979 (Box 580)
        - Be - BZ (B), 1979-1980 (Box 580)
        - C (B), 1978-1979 (Box 581)
        - D (B), 1978-1979 (Box 581)
        - E-F (B), 1978-1979 (Box 581)
        - G (B), 1978-1979 (Box 581)
        - H (B), 1978-1979 (Box 581)
        - I,J,K, 1978-1979 (Box 582)
        - L (B), 1978-1979 (Box 582)
        - M (B), 1978-1979 (Box 582)
        - N-P (B), 1979 (Box 582)
        - Q-R (B), 1979 (Box 582)
        - S (B), 1979 (Box 583)
        - T-Z (B), 1979 (Box 583)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1979-1981 (Box 583)
    - [Miscellaneous] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 583)
    - [Miscellaneous letters] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 583)
    - [Solar] (B), 1979 (Box 583)
    - Southern Connecticut Energy Meeting, 1979 June 22 (Box 583)
    - Stonington Meeting, 1979 (Box 583)
    - Volunteer Service Organizations Fuel Needs (B), 1979 (Box 583)
    - [Frisbee - Hearthstone] (B), 1979 (Box 583)
    - [Letters] (Box 583)
      - A-C (B), 1978-1980 (Box 583)
      - D-E (B), 1978-1979 (Box 584)
      - F-K (B), 1978-1980 (Box 584)
      - L-M (B), 1979-1980 (Box 584)
      - N-P (B), 1979-1980 (Box 584)
      - Q-Z (B), 1978-1980 (Box 584)
    - [Memos to and from Burns] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 584)
    - [Memos to and from Milano], 1978-1980 (Box 585)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1979 (Box 585)
    - [Nuclear Power], 1978-1980 (Box 585)
    - [Nuclear Regulatory Agency], 1978-1980 (Box 585)
  - [Office of Personnel Management - Federal], 1980 (Box 585)
  - Official Statement - Muhammed Ali to Hartford (B), 1979 (Box 585)
  - [Oil - Home Heating] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 585)
  - Oil - Letters for Governor from oil Companies (I), 1979 (Box 585)
  - [O’Neill Miscellaneous] (I), 1981 (Box 585)
  - [Opticians/Optometry] (B), 1979 (Box 585)
  - Pavane Presentation, 1978 (Box 586)
  - [Personnel] (Box 586)
    - Clerical job classification (B), 1979 March (Box 586)
    - Collective bargaining contracts, 1977 (Box 586)
    - Collective bargaining private file, 1978-1979 (Box 586)
    - [Letters] (Box 586)
      - A-B (B), 1978-1979 (Box 586)
      - C-F (B), 1978-1980 (Box 586)
      - G-L (B), 1979-1980 (Box 587)
      - M-Q (B), 1979-1980 (Box 587)
      - R-Z, 1979-1980 (Box 587)
    - [Memos to and from Biloon], 1979-1980 (Box 587)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1979-1980 (Box 587)
    - Retirement Benefits for the State Employees (General) (B) (Box 587)
    - Strike by State Employees, 1979 (Box 587)
    - [Suggestion Awards] (B), 1979 (Box 587)
    - [Summer Employment], 1979 (Box 587)
  - [Pharmacy Commission], 1979 (Box 587)
  - [Physical Fitness], 1978-1980 (Box 587)
  - [Police Matter] (B), 1979 (Box 587)
  - [Politics - Election], 1979-1980 (Box 587)
  - [Politics - Election, Open Convention], 1980 (Box 588)
  - [Pornography] (B), 1979 (Box 588)
  - [Postal Service] (B), 1979 (Box 588)
  - [Power Facility Evaluation Council], 1979-1980 (Box 588)
  - President Carter’s Inauguration, 1976-1977 (Box 588)
  - [President’s Anti-inflation Program] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 588)
  - President’s Reorganization Project, 1978-1979 (Box 588)
  - [Press] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 588)
  - Press/ “Ask the Governor” - WTIC, 1979 June 23 (Box 588)
  - [Probate Court] (B), 1979 (Box 588)
  - [Proclamations], 1979 (Box 588)
  - [Public Expenditure Council], 1979-1980 (Box 588)
  - [Public Safety] (Box 588)
    - Budget (B), 1979 (Box 588)
    - [Memos to and from Long], 1978-1980 (Box 588)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1978-1980 (Box 588)
    - Speeding (B), 1978-1979 (Box 588)
    - [State Police Letters] (Box 588)
      - A-D (B), 1979-1980 (Box 588)
      - E-K (B), 1978-1979 (Box 588)
      - L-M (Box 588)
      - N-S, 1978-1979 (Box 589)
      - T-Z (Box 589)
  - [Public TV - CPTV], 1978-1979 (Box 589)
  - [Public Utilities Control Authority - PUCA] (Box 589)
    - Advertising by Public Utility Companies (B), 1979 (Box 589)
    - [CLP/HELCO], 1980 (Box 589)
    - [CNG], 1980 (Box 589)
    - Directory Assistance Charge, 1978 (Box 589)
    - Harrisburg Assistance Charge, 1978 (Box 589)
    - [Letters] (Box 589)
      - A-E (B), 1978-1981 (Box 589)
      - F-K (B), 1978-1981 (Box 589)
      - L-R (B), 1978-1981 (Box 590)
      - S-Z (B), 1978-1980 (Box 590)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1979-1980 (Box 590)
    - [Moratorium Policy], 1978 (Box 590)
    - New Britain to Hartford - Toll free service (B), 1978-1979 (Box 590)
    - [Northeast Utilities (NU) - Letters] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 590)
    - [NU - Millstone], 1977-1979 (Box 590)
    - [NU - Miscellaneous], 1979 (Box 590)
    - [Letters] (Box 591)
      - [NU Miscellaneous], 1980-1981 (Box 591)
      - [NU - Nuclear Regulatory Agency], 1979-1980 (Box 591)
      - [So. Conn. Gas Co.], 1979-1980 (Box 591)
      - [Telephone], 1979-1980 (Box 591)
      - [United Illuminating], 1978-1979 (Box 591)
      - [United Illuminating], 1980 (Box 591)
      - Yankee Atomic Power Co., 1979 (Box 591)
  - Public Works - Juvenile Detention Center on Whalley Avenue in New Haven (B), 1979 (Box 591)
  - [Public Works - Letters] (B), 1979 (Box 591)
  - Purchasing Bureau (B), 1979 (Box 591)
  - [Questionnaire] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 591)
  - [Real Estate Commission] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 592)
  - [Recommendation - Miscellaneous] (B), 1978-1980 (Box 592)
  - Recommendation Winthrop Rockefeller Award (B), 1979 (Box 592)
  - [Red Cross], 1978-1979 (Box 592)
  - [Retention], 1978 (Box 592)
  - [Regrets - Israel Trip] (O), 1978 (Box 592)
  - Reorganization - Abolishment of Boards Councils (O), 1978 (Box 592)
    - of the Executive Branch of State Government, 1977 (Box 592)
    - of the State Government, 1978-1979 (Box 592)
    - of the State Government Luncheon - Residence (O), 1979 January 12 (Box 592)
  - [Requests] (B), 1978-1980 (Box 592)
  - Residence, 1979 (Box 592)
  - Residence/Meeting to Discuss Problems Confronting the (O) (Box 592)
  - Hispanic Community, 1978 (Box 592)
  - [Resignations] (B), 1979 (Box 592)
  - [Restitution Commission] (B), 1978-1979 (Box 592)
  - [Resume] - Christie law, 1979 (Box 592)
  - [Resumes - Letters] (Box 592)